krispykreme.com 2019-05-03

# Krispy Kreme - Legal | Privacy Policy

## Krispy Kreme Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the information privacy practices of Krispy Kreme Doughnut Corporation (referred to herein as “Krispy Kreme”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). It explains what information we collect about you, how we use and share your information, and your choices regarding our collection and use.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us as provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

  * Scope of Privacy Policy
  * Changes To Our Privacy Policy
  * Information Collected
  * How We Use Your Information
  * How We Share Your Information
  * Cookies and Other Technologies
  * Your Choices
  * Information Security
  * User Generated Content
  * Links, Third Party Websites, and Social Media Platforms
  * California Residents’ Privacy Rights
  * Do Not Track Notice
  * Users Outside the United States
  * Children’s Privacy
  * Email Security
  * Contact Us

## Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected about you by or on behalf of Krispy Kreme when you use our website located at https://www.krispykreme.com or any other website or mobile application owned, operated or controlled by us that posts a link to this Privacy Policy (our “Sites”), as well as any programs, features, services, or transactions provided through our Sites (collectively, with our Sites, our “Online Services”). This Privacy Policy also applies when you communicate with us via email or otherwise through the Internet.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the information privacy practices of franchised Krispy Kreme shops, which Krispy Kreme does not own or operate, or to other independent third parties.

## Changes To Our Privacy Policy

Krispy Kreme may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices or in applicable law. Such changes will be effective upon posting the revised Privacy Policy, along with the date on which it was most recently updated, on our Sites. You will be able to tell when this Privacy Policy was last updated by the Last Updated date included at the top of this Privacy Policy. If a change materially affects the use or disclosure of your personally identifiable information, we will provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the homepage on our Sites or sending you an email notification). By continuing to use our Online Services or communicating electronically with us thereafter, you agree to accept such changes to this Privacy Policy. Please contact us as provided at the end of this Privacy Policy if you would like information regarding any changes.

## Information Collected

Krispy Kreme collects information about you from a variety of sources, including information you provide directly to us when you sign-up for Krispy Kreme rewards or request information from us, and information we collect about you when you access and use our Online Services. The information we collect includes both personally identifiable information and other information that cannot be used to personally identifiable you.

Information You Provide Us. If you sign-up for Krispy Kreme rewards, submit a fundraising order form, place an advanced order, purchase gift cards or other collectibles, request information or apply for a job through our Online Services, or communicate with us electronically, we collect the requested information that you provide including your name, e-mail, phone number, address, birthdate, and demographic information. You may choose whether or not to provide such information; however, the information may be required to utilize certain features of our Online Services. If you apply for a job online with Krispy Kreme, we also collect background check information in processing your application.

Information Collected Automatically. We collect information automatically from you when you visit our Sites, use our Online Services, and in connection with our emails, online advertisements, and social media pages. Such information includes the following:

Usage information. We collect information about how you interact with our Online Services. This includes information such as the dates and times that you visit our Sites, the page you view, referring / exit URLs, your browser type, and the number of clicks on our Sites. In some cases, we collect this information through cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies. To learn more about these technologies, please see the Cookies and Other Technologies section below.

Device Information. We collect information about the devices you use to access our Online Services, including your device model, IP address, operating system, unique device identifiers, and mobile network operator information.

Transaction Information. We collect transaction details related to your use of certain Online Services such as the rewards program, advanced ordering, delivery, and purchase of gift cards and collectables.

Location Information. We may collect location information including the real-time geographic location of your device through data such as your GPS coordinates, IP address, and WiFi.

Information We Receive From Third Parties. We may receive information about you from third parties such as our business partners and service providers, including payment processors, marketing service providers, and franchisees.

## How We Use Your Information

Krispy Kreme uses your information, including personally identifiable information, for a variety of business purposes, including:

  * providing our Online Services;
  * processing your transactions;
  * creating and managing your account;
  * communicating with you;
  * processing your applications for fundraising and employment;
  * responding to your inquiries and communications;
  * customer service and technical support, which may include responding to your requests, resolving issues, and/or troubleshooting problems;
  * improving and customizing our Online Services, communications, and advertisements;
  * for internal operations such as enhancing our offerings and to conduct research and analysis;
  * for marketing purposes;
  * to assist in loss prevention and anti-fraud measures;
  * to enforce our Terms of Use, and any other applicable terms and conditions and agreements;
  * to comply with applicable laws, regulations, and legal processes; and/or
  * to protect the security and integrity of our business, Online Services, products, services, brands, users, customers, and third party business partners and service providers.

## How We Share Your Information

Krispy Kreme shares and discloses your information, including personally identifiable information, under the following circumstances:

  * with third parties that provide a variety of services on our behalf, including the development, hosting, maintenance, and support of our Online Services; processing your transactions and payments; data management, storage, and analysis; communications; and marketing;
  * with franchisees in order to provide our products, services, and promotions to you, and for marketing purposes;
  * to comply with law, a court order, or other legal process, or in connection with a legal investigation;
  * as may be necessary to protect the rights and interests of Krispy Kreme, its third party business partners and service providers, and our and their respective employees, customers, visitors, users, or any other person or entity;
  * to enforce our Terms of Use, and any other applicable terms and conditions and other agreements;
  * in the event of a corporate transaction, including a merger, acquisition, financing, dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving the sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of Krispy Kreme’s business or assets. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, your personally identifiable information may also be transferred as a business asset of Krispy Kreme. If another third party acquires Krispy Kreme or any of it business operations, whether through stock or asset purchase, such third party will possess the information, including personally identifiable information, collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations with respect thereto as described in this Privacy Policy;
  * in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable form; and/or
  * in accordance with your consent.

## Cookies and Other Technologies

We and our business partners and third party providers use cookies and other technologies such as log files, web beacons, and analytic tools and services on our Sites and other Online Services and in our email communications and online advertisements to collect information automatically from you. Such information includes your IP address, device type, any unique device identification numbers, type of browser (e.g., Google Chrome or Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows, Vista, Mac, OS, Android, etc.), your browsing activities (e.g., pages viewed and referring / exit URLs), location information, and other usage information. We collect this information for a number of reasons, including optimization of our Sites, improving our Online Services, to enhance your user experience, remembering user preferences and settings, marketing and advertising purposes, security purposes, and analyzing Site traffic and trends.

Please see below for more information regarding the technologies that we may use.

Cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device. We use cookies to collect information from you regarding your usage of our Online Services in order to remember user preferences and settings, personalize your experience with our Online Services, and for security purposes.

Log File Information. Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile device each time you access our Online Services. The information collected from log files may include your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, landing pages, and pages viewed.

Web Beacons. We may also use web beacons (also known as a “pixel tag” or “clear gif”) which are small blocks of code installed on or utilized with our Online Services, emails, and online advertisements which can retrieve certain information about your device and browser, and other usage information.

Social Media Features. Our Sites contain social media features such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These features may collect information such as your IP address and the pages you are visiting on our Sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing the applicable feature.

Online Analytics. We may use third party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for our Online Services. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit and other usage information. For more information regarding how Google collects, uses, and shares your information please visit <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

## Your Choices

Krispy Kreme provides you with the opportunity to update and/or delete certain personally identifiable information and to opt-out of having information collected for certain purposes. For example, you may

  * update your account information;
  * delete your account;
  * choose whether to receive promotions and offers from us;
  * change your preferences for certain communications; and
  * request access to your personally identifiable information.

You may exercise your choices by contacting us via the Contact Us information provided below or following the instructions provided in the electronic communications sent to you.

Because we plan our communications in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications after expressing an opt-out preference, please let us know so that we can investigate the situation. We will, however, continue to send transaction-based emails if you engage in a transaction, request customer support, or make similar requests.

In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you may not be able to utilize certain features of our Online Services.

Location Information. You may opt-out from allowing us to have access to your location data by adjusting the permissions in your web browser and mobile device. However, some features of our Online Services may not function properly if use or availability of location data is impaired or disabled.

Cookies and Other Technologies. You may opt-out of the automatic collection of some information by referring to your web browser’s or mobile device’s options or settings menu. However, doing so may disable many of the portions, features, or functionality of our Online Services. For example, most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you have the choice to set your browser to accept or reject cookies. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences or visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org for more information.

Google Analytics. Google provides users choice on how their data is collected by Google Analytics by developing an Opt-out Browser Add-on which can be located at:[ ](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. By installing this Add-on, no information is being sent to Google.

## Information Security

Krispy Kreme implements reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to help us protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. However, no method of electronically transmitting or storing data is ever completely secure, and therefore, we cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable information will never be accessed, used, or disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

## User Generated Content

Krispy Kreme’s Online Services and social media pages may allow you to post messages and submit content (e.g., comments, blogs, photos, postings, etc.), which may include your personally identifiable information. You are responsible for all actions resulting from any information, including personally identifiable information, which you post on our Online Services or social media pages. Please remember that any information you post becomes public information, is not subject to this Privacy Policy, and Krispy Kreme is not responsible for the results of such postings.

## Links, Third Party Websites, and Social Media Platforms

Krispy Kreme’s Online Services and electronic communications may contain links to third party websites and social media platforms such as Facebook or Twitter (including, without limitation, franchisee websites or social media pages), and our products and services may be advertised and/or offered on third party websites (“Linked Sites”). We are not responsible for the privacy practices, policies, or content of any Linked Sites, even if you link to them from our Online Services or communications. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Linked Sites. We have no control over the collection or use of your information on any Linked Site. We encourage you to read and understand the privacy practices of any Linked Sites that you visit.

## California Residents’ Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed certain personal information (as defined by California law) during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact us via the Contact Us information provided below. For all requests, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information. Please allow 30 days for a response.

## Do Not Track Notice

At this time, there is no worldwide uniform or consistent industry standard or definition for responding to, processing, or communicating Do Not Track signals. Thus, like many other websites and online services, our Online Services are currently unable to respond to Do Not Track Signals. To find out more about “Do Not Track”, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

## Users Outside the United States

Our Online Services and electronic communications are provided from within the United States and are subject to the applicable state and federal laws of the United States. If you use our Online Services from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, or processed in the United States where our servers are located and our database is operated. The data protections and other laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. We will rely on legally-provided mechanisms to lawfully transfer personally identifiable information across borders.

## Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 without verified parental or guardian consent. Please contact us as provided below in the Contact Us section if you believe we may have collected such information without parental or guardian consent.

## Email Security

“Phishing” is a scam designed to steal your personally identifiable information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from Krispy Kreme asking you for your personally identifiable information, including account information, please notify us as provided below.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Krispy Kreme’s information privacy practices, please contact us at:

E-mail: [krispykreme@casupport.com](mailto:krispykreme@casupport.com)  
Mail: Krispy Kreme Doughnut Corporation  
370 Knollwood Street  
Winston-Salem, North Carolina 27103  
Attn: Legal Department
